I don't know about y'all, but I'm just deeply disturbed by the fact that the aid workers working with the WCK, the World Central Kitchen, went to Gaza under the auspices that there had been an agreement between Israel and America to keep them safe.
The whole point of them going to Gaza was for the point of being the one way that aid could make it in that had been approved by Israel.
Their van was shot with a missile. They got out. The ones who were alive went to the next van. That one was shot with a missile.
They carried the hurt to the next van and that one was shot with a missile. There were three different strikes.
And now the World Central Kitchen has suspended its aid and the two aid ships coming from Cyprus have turned around.
So the people of Gaza are still in the same situation they were in.
And Netanyahu's response to this was, well, you know, this is what happens in war.
Then you have people who are representing the White House look the press dead in their face and say, I mean, this was an accident.
I mean, it was it was not calculated in the press corps.
I commend all of y'all for not jumping up and being like, yo, what are you doing?
Because I've never seen a global playing in the face as what is happening right now.
So, let's see.